KEVIN YEUNG

12 Tanglewood Drive, Saint Albans, Vermont 05478 (+1)802-582-8436 ♦ kevinyeung1999@outlook.com

EDUCATION

University of Vermont, Burlington

August 2017 - Present

Bachelors and Accelerated Masters in Computer Science

ABOUT ME

Full time computer science student at University of Vermont. I have experience working in industries including health, tech, and business through part-time jobs and shadows. I am currently working on finishing my undergrad and finding an internship in my field to begin my career. Outside academics I enjoy playing sports, watching movies, creating YouTube videos.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Saint Albans Recreational Department

June 2017 - August 2019

Counselor

· Collaborated with 5-10 coworkers to supervise, engage, and direct groups of children between the ages of 5 and 14. Worked with administrators and social service employees to coordinate activities for over 80 kids on a regular basis. Communicated with parents and service providers to create a fun and safe environment for each child.

Securitas

January 2019 - May 2019

Security Officer

· Operated in a team of four to provide a safe and secure environment for patients and employees. Trained for high-risk situations including fires, health-based emergencies, armed intrusions, and bomb threats. Helped guide prospective candidates and communicated with hospital administration in planning patrols and patient one-on-ones. Collaborated with law enforcement and child services to create daily reports.

JL Snackshop

April 2016 - April 2017

General Store Manager

· Maintained a general store independently and at times with one other co-worker. I processed financial information and parsed business reports daily. Cooperated with prospective hires and guided new employees through troubleshooting techniques and billing procedures.

Eastern Dragon

July 2015 - April 2016

Head Waiter

· Worked with a large team to provide exceptional service to customers. Cooperated regularly with executives and other businesses to maintain professionalism and uphold service standards.

SKILLS/STRENGTHS

Technical

Computer (Hardware/Software) Technology, Design, Marketing

Soft

Leadership, Team-Member, Organization, Communication, Problem-Solving

EXTRA CURRICULAR

- UVM Film Crew, Club Soccer, Gaming Club, CS Crew, Society of Physics Students
- Volunteer at Tim's Place, Humane Society, Red Cross, Salvation Army
- Founder of Homebrew, an easy-to-use website for smaller vendors to sell products online